Hai Long Pham, Marketing Executive

Tel.: +84 367084361 , Email: hailongpham3012@gmail.com, DOB: 30/12/2000, Addr.: Long Bien, Hanoi

PROFILE

Fluent in English and experienced working for international IT businesses that specialize in FinTech & Ecommerce (AI & Shopify). High commitment to learn, work and grow in marketing and business professions.

Good communication skills, both written and verbally. Able to work well independently and as a group member. Good integration ability allows for coping with pressure and new environments.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Nov 2020 - Jan 2020

Product Marketing Executive, Nexus Frontier Tech

Hanoi

Write various forms of content to support product activation, from website, blog articles, social media posts, ad copies, email marketing campaigns, brochures, case studies to white papers.

Perform market research in finance, technology and other related fields. Perform keyword & target customer research to assist with SEO and advertising practices.

Play a crucial role in re-branding the company's core product, plan and coordinate with marketing & sales to launch a new solution. Work with different teams stationed in Singapore, Japan & the UK.

Apr 2020 — Sep 2020

Marketing Executive, Hamsa Technologies

Hanoi

Perform market research and assist in various product development tasks.

Craft content including blog articles, social media posts & email automation. Perform on-page SEO and seeding for said content.

Execute advertising campaigns using Google Ads and Shopify Ads. Assist graphic designers in creating logos, banners and related media publications. Manage the company's social media.

Compile and analyze data and develop plans for future marketing campaigns. Contribute to the launch of 02 Shopify apps in both marketing & development area.

Oct 2019 — Apr 2020

Marketing & Copywriting Associate, Do Creative

Hanoi

Develop and implement marketing content, ideas & projects to support the clients' needs and objectives.

Perform market research, data management & document translation using various applications and tools. Manage clients' and the company's social media presence and basic Facebook advertising.

Assist with the company's daily activities and other ad hoc tasks as required.

EDUCATION

Oct 2016 — Aug 2019

Bachelor of Business in Marketing and International Business, Murdoch University

Singapore

A 3-year double-major bachelor degree program at one of the best universities in the world. Graduated at 18 years old.

The program provided fundamental knowledge of international marketing and businesses through 24 modules, taught by acclaimed professors and successful business professionals.

SKILLS	Microsoft Office/G Suite	Expert	Email Marketing	Expert
	Marketing Research	Expert	Google, FB & LinkedIn Ads	Skillful
	Content Marketing	Expert	SEO/SEM	Skillful
	Marketing Strategy	Experienced	CRM (Freshsales, Hubspot)	Experienced
	Data Analysis	Skillful	Social Media Management	Experienced

REFERENCES